[SPEAKER_00]: Huge cave entrance.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, huge entrance and a huge cave.
[SPEAKER_00]: What are they?
[SPEAKER_00]: The bats?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, yeah, they're there.
[SPEAKER_00]: As long as you don't shine directly onto the ceiling and they'll ignore us, mostly.
[SPEAKER_00]: Very thick one as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: Very, very, I know, I can feel it.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the only way, basically, to the left, up here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wow, look at that.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's about 40 meters there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Can you find me a little branch?
[SPEAKER_00]: He's just sitting there now.
[SPEAKER_00]: It would have been a painful journey back down.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just want him to turn the head if he can.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, he's going.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, that is stunning.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just gently, just gently.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't poke him.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just gently.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, if you stand in the front, he'll wait.
[SPEAKER_00]: Going a bit fancy.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's gonna strike my phone.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's pumping.
[SPEAKER_00]: And this is the full size, by the way.
[SPEAKER_00]: Check it out, against my hand.
[SPEAKER_00]: Tiny.
[SPEAKER_00]: And they cause kidney failure.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like very mild local symptoms, just you swell, pain, but they cause organ damage internally.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, there is no antivenom for this.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, you might just have to go to hospital to be looked after in case of complications, you know, antibiotics, infections and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_00]: That could have been a... Well, you almost stepped on it, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_00]: Try and get him out a bit more.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right, that's right.
[SPEAKER_00]: That is so pretty.
[SPEAKER_00]: Look at the size of that thickness.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll let you go in a second, but I just want to see how big you are.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's it.